Guide to the John Franklin Enders Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and Topical Files, 1916-1988; Series I; 36.75' (88 boxes)
  - Armed Forces Epidemiological Board
    - Contract DA-49-007-MD-474
      - Authorized signatures, 1956, undated (Box 6, Folder 102)
      - Contracts, 1953-1962 (Box 6, Folder 103)
      - Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Box 6, Folder 104)
      - Correspondence, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 105)
      - Correspondence, 1960, undated (Box 6, Folder 106)
      - Final report, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 107)
      - Subject inventories, 1957-1960 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Contract DA-49-143-MD-2438: Annual progress reports, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Measles: reports and reprints, 1965, undated (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Measles: reports and reprints, undated (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Notification of personnel action, 1951-1968 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Request for obtaining serum from monkeys, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Research and technology resume, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Security investigation data, 1957, 1966, undated (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Spring meeting notes: 1965 Mar, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Travel, 1954-1966 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Armed Forces Institute of Pathology, 1955-1963, undated (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - Armour and Company, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Armstrong, C. F. W., 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 120)
  - Armstrong, Donald, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 121)
  - Armstrong, Howard, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Arnold, John H., 1954-1969, undated (Box 7, Folder 123-124)
  - Associated Harvard Clubs, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - Atanasiu, Pascu, 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Atkinson, LeRoy, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Atlantic Monthly, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Aub, Joseph C., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Avery, Mary Ellen, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Aycock, William Lloyd, 1951-1952, undated (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Ayer, Fredrick, 1964, undated (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Azer, Paul M., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Backman, John Herbert, 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Baer, George M., 1970-1974, undated (Box 7, Folder 136)
  - Bailey, Percival, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 137)
  - Baker-Channing Society, 1959, undated (Box 7, Folder 138)
  - Baldwin, Sherman, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 139)
  - Banatvala, J. E., 1973, undated (Box 7, Folder 140)
  - Bang, Frederick B., 1957-1964, 1969, 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Barger, Clifford A., 1970 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Baringer, J. R., 1970, undated (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Baron, Samuel, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Barry, Herbert, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Barski, Georges, 1958, 1962, undated (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Baver, Walter, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Bayreuther, Klaus, 1962, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Bazeley, P. L., 1950-1952, 1957, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Beck, Claude S., 1962, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 150)
  - Beecher, Henry K., 1960, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Beers, Henry S., 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Beladi, Ilona, 1971-1972, undated (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Bell, E. John, 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Benirschke, Kurt, 1957-1960, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Benison, Saul, 1955, 1962-1963, 1967, 1974, undated (Box 8, Folder 156)
  - Benjamin, Thomas L., 1965, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 157)
  - Berg, Gerald, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 158)
  - Berg, Robert B., 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 159)
  - Berg, Robert B., 1960-1964, undated (Box 8, Folder 160)
  - Bergamini, Fernanda, 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 161)
  - Berge, Trygve O., 1964, undated (Box 8, Folder 162)
  - Bergel, F., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 163)
  - Bergs, Victor, 1955-1956, undated (Box 8, Folder 164)
  - Bering, Edgar A., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 165)
  - Berkovich, Sumner, 1945, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 166-167)
  - Berkovich, Sumner, 1965-1972, 1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 168)
  - Berman, Herbert J., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 169)
  - Bernier, George M., 1957, undated (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Berry, George Packer, 1960-1966, undated (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - Berson, Eliot, 1960-1968, undated (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Beselin, Oskar, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Bier, Otto, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Bing, Richard J., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Biological Abstracts, 1946, 1957, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 176)
  - Bishop, Michael, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 177)
  - Bissell, Alfred, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 178)
  - Björklund, Bertil, 1960,1963 (Box 9, Folder 179)
  - Black, Francis L., 1972, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 180)
    See also: box 47, folder 1162
  - Black, Paul H., 1964-1969, 1973-1974, undated (Box 9, Folder 181)
  - Blalock, Alfred, 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 182)
  - Blanchard, Leon, 1961, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 183)
  - Bloch, Konrad, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 184)
  - Blood Cells and Plasma Proteins, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 185)
  - Bodanov, I. L., 1961, undated (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Bodian, David, 1951-1952 (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Boggs, Joseph
    See: box 32, folder 765
  - Bogoch, Samuel, 1958-1962, 1966, undated (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Bok, Derek C., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Bolande, Robert P., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Bongiovanni, Alfred M., 1966, undated (Box 9, Folder 191)
  - Borecky, Ladislav, 1961-1963, undated (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Borek, Ernest, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 193)
  - Bornstein, Murray B., 1955 (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - Boston Bacteriological Club, 1954-1955, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - Boston City Hospital
    - General, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 196)
    - House Officer's Assn., 1947, 1951, 1961-1962 (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Boston Committee for Medical Emigres, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 198)
  - Boston Daily Globe, 1958, undated (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Boston Health Department, 1953, 1961, undated (Box 9, Folder 200)
  - Boston Hospital for Women, 1967-1975, undated (Box 9, Folder 201)
  - Boston Lying-In Hospital, 1947-1954, 1965, 1970-1974, undated (Box 9, Folder 202)
  - Boston Medical Foundation, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 203)
  - Boston Medical Library, 1953-1957, 1960, 1965, undated (Box 9, Folder 204)
  - Bouillant, Alain, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 205)
  - Boyd, Harriet, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Boyd, William C., 1956, 1960, undated (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Branch, Arnold, 1955-1957, undated (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Bratt, Michael A., 1970-1973, undated (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Breast milk data, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 210)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 211)
  - British Medical Association, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - British Medical Journal, 1955, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 213)
  - Bronfman Prize, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 214)
  - Brooke, Marcus, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 215)
  - Broome, Mildred, 1971-1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 216)
  - Büchi, G., 1964-1965 (Box 10, Folder 217)
  - Buggs, C. W., 1957 (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - Bunts, Alexander, 1947-1950, 1954-1964, 1967, undated (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - Burket, Anne E., 1958 1965, undated (Box 10, Folder 220)
  - Burlingham, Carlos E., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 221)
  - Burnet, F. M., 1947-1958, 1962-1963, 1969-1974, undated (Box 10, Folder 222)
  - Burnett, Joseph W., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Burwell, C. Sidney, 1946, 1961-1962, 1965-1967,undated (Box 10, Folder 224)
  - Cabasso, Victor J., 1946, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 225)
  - Cade, Stanford, 1957-1958 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Caliguiri, Lawrence A., 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Cambridge City Hospital, 1965-1970, undated (Box 10, Folder 228-230)
  - Cambridge Scientific Club, 1956-1969 (Box 10, Folder 231-232)
  - Cambridge Scientific Club, 1970-1976, 1980, undated (Box 11, Folder 233)
  - Cameron Prize, 1959-1960 (Box 11, Folder 234)
  - Cameron Prize, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 235)
  - Campbell, Charlotte, 1966, 1972, undated (Box 11, Folder 236)
  - Campillo-Sainz, Carlos, 1952-1960, 1963-1964, 1967, 1972, undated (Box 11, Folder 237)
  - Camprubi, José, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 238)
  - Cancer
    - Cancer Research and Training Committee of Harvard University, 1950-1958, undated (Box 11, Folder 239-242)
    - Children's Cancer Research Foundation Scientific Program, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 243)
    - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1960-1961, 1965-1968, undated (Box 11, Folder 244)
    - National Cancer Conference, 1963-1966, undated (Box 11, Folder 245)
    - Panel on Viruses and Cancer
      - General, 1958-1961, undated (Box 12, Folder 246-248)
      - Radiation studies in primates, 1953-1956, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 249)
      - U. S. S. R. report on etiology (pp. 1-186), undated (Box 12, Folder 250)
      - U. S. S. R. report on etiology (pp. 187-372), undated (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - Quacks, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 252)
    - Senate committee, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 253)
    - Virus and Cancer Symposium, 1960-1961, undated (Box 12, Folder 254)
  - Carbide and Carbon Chemicals Corporation, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 255)
  - Cardinali, Giuseppe, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 256)
  - Carey, Benjamin, 1942, 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 257)
  - Caribetses, John, 1957-1958 (Box 12, Folder 258)
  - Carleton, Henry G., 1949 (Box 12, Folder 259)
  - Carne, H. R., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 260)
  - Carson, Paul E., 1946-1951, 1956-1962, undated (Box 12, Folder 261)
  - Carver, David H., 1959-1977, undated (Box 13, Folder 262-265)
  - Carworth Farms, Inc., 1939 (Box 13, Folder 266)
  - Castañeda, M. Ruiz, 1938-1942, 1947, 1952-1956, 1959, undated (Box 13, Folder 267)
  - Castle, William B., 1958, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 268)
  - Cerebral Palsy, 1957, undated (Box 13, Folder 269)
  - Chandler, Caroline A., 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 270)
  - Chang, Charles C., 1954 (Box 13, Folder 271)
  - Chang, Robert S., 1957-1962, 1967-1968, 1972, undated (Box 13, Folder 272-273)
  - Chang, S. L., 1944, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 274)
  - Chanock, Robert M., 1949, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 275)
  - Chany, Charles, 1948, 1960-1965, 1974-1975, undated (Box 13, Folder 276)
  - Chapman, Carleton B., 1967, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 277)
  - Chapman, Earle M., 1945, 1947, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 278)
  - Charles C. Thomas, Publisher, 1949-1951, 1957-1961, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 279)
  - Charles Pfizer and Company, 1957, 1961, 1966, undated (Box 13, Folder 280)
  - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1965, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 281)
  - Cheatham, William J., 1952-1960, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 282)
  - Cheever, David, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - Cheever, F. Sargent, 1939-1964, 1970, 1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 284-286)
  - Cheney, Ward, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Folder 287)
  - Chernin, Eli, 1957, 1960, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 288)
  - Children's Hospital (Winnipeg, Canada), 1947-1948 (Box 14, Folder 289)
  - Children's Hospital Medical Center (Boston)
    - Correspondence, general, 1946-1955, 1959-1976, 1982, undated (Box 14, Folder 290-291)
    - Diagnostic Viral Laboratory, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 292)
    - Enders Pediatric Research Laboratories, 1969-1972, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 293)
    - Enders Research Fund, 1962-1966, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - Farber, Sidney, 1946-1970, 1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 295-296)
    - Gifts, 1961-1964, 1970-1974 (Box 14, Folder 297)
    - Infectious disease follow-up clinic, 1948, undated (Box 14, Folder 298)
    - Portrait Fund
      See: box 72, folder 1608
    - Research Administration, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 299)
    - Research Division of Infectious Diseases
      - General, 1946-1951, 1955-1971, 1974, undated (Box 14, Folder 300-301)
      - Annual reports, 1947-1962, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 302-303)
      - Research fellowships, 1951-1968, undated (Box 15, Folder 304)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01192-06, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 305)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01192-07, 1963, 1965, undated (Box 15, Folder 306)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-08, 1964-1966 (Box 15, Folder 307)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-09, 1964-1967 (Box 15, Folder 308)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-10, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 309)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-11, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 310)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-12, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 311)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-13, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 312)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-14, 1970-1972 (Box 15, Folder 313)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-15, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 314)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-16, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 315)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # AI-01992-17, 1973-1974 (Box 15, Folder 316)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # E1992, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 317)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # E1992 (C1), 1957-1959 (Box 16, Folder 318)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # E1992 (C2), 1959 (Box 16, Folder 319)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # E1992 (C3), 1960-1962 (Box 16, Folder 320)
      - U. S. Public Health Service research grant # E1992 (C4), 1961-1963, undated (Box 16, Folder 321)
      - U. S. Public Health Service Research Grants Effort reports, 1963-1968 (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - Staff, 1946-1961 (Box 16, Folder 323)
    - Staff, 1965-1972 (Box 16, Folder 324)
    - Surgical grand rounds, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 325)
    - Virology advisory committee, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 326)
    - Virus Research Unit: bibliography, 1957-1976 (Box 16, Folder 327)
  - Children's Hospital of Philadelphia, 1952 (Box 16, Folder 328)
  - Children's Hospital Research Foundation (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1954-1960 (Box 16, Folder 329)
  - Christian, Henry A., 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 330)
  - Chumakov, Mikhail Petrovich, 1956, 1959, 1965-1970 (Box 16, Folder 331)
  - Chumakov, Mikhail Petrovich, undated (Box 16, Folder 332)
  - Church, Karen, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 333)
  - Chute, Richard, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 334)
  - CIBA Pharmaceutical Products, 1957-1964, 1969, undated (Box 16, Folder 335)
  - Cinader, Bernhard, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 336)
  - Clark, Paul F., 1961 (Box 16, Folder 337)
  - Clemens, Cyril, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 338)
  - Clifford, Stewart H., 1964, undated (Box 16, Folder 339)
  - Cobb, Robert C., 1960, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 340)
  - Cobb, Stanley, 1946, 1954-1955, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Coca, Arthur F., 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 342)
  - Cockburn, Charles, 1951 (Box 17, Folder 343)
  - Cockrill, Jesse Reed, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 344)
  - Cogan, David G., 1946, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 345)
  - Cohen, Seymour S., 1963 (Box 17, Folder 346)
  - Cohn, Edwin J., 1938-1948 (Box 17, Folder 347)
  - College of American Pathologists, 1948, 1961, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 348)
  - College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 349)
  - Collier, Leslie H., 1954-1955, 1967, 1970, undated (Box 17, Folder 350)
  - Collins, Jeffrey J., 1970-1974, undated (Box 17, Folder 351)
  - Columbia University. College of Physicians and Surgeons, 1955-1956, 1966, 1968, undated (Box 17, Folder 352)
  - Comanduras, Peter D., 1966 (Box 17, Folder 353)
  - Commission on Measles and Mumps
    See: box 55, folders 1308-1315
  - Common cold, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 354)
  - Communicable Disease Center, 1957, 1961-1966, undated (Box 17, Folder 355)
  - Concordia Foundation Trust, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 356)
  - Condie, Frances, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 357)
  - Condry, Paul B., 1945 (Box 17, Folder 358)
  - Conference of State and Provincial Public Health Laboratory Directors, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 359)
  - Congress for Cultural Freedom, 1956, undated (Box 17, Folder 360)
  - Congresso Internacional de Pediátria, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 361)
  - Connecticut College, 1955-1956 (Box 17, Folder 362)
  - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1955, 1970-1972, undated (Box 17, Folder 363)
  - Coons, Albert H., 1942-1944 (Box 17, Folder 364)
  - Coons, Albert H., 1947, 1952-1953, 1957, 1968-1972 (Box 17, Folder 365)
  - Coons, Albert H., 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 366)
  - Coons, Albert H., undated (Box 17, Folder 367)
  - Cooper, Alan J., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 368)
  - Cooper, Louis Z., 1969-1971 (Box 17, Folder 369)
  - Cooper, Merlin L., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 370)
  - Cooper, Peter D., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 371)
  - Cope, Oliver, 1945, 1964-1966 (Box 17, Folder 372)
  - Coriell, Lewis L., 1963-1964, 1967, undated (Box 17, Folder 373)
  - Cornell University Press, 1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 374)
  - Corson, Samuel A., 1944 (Box 17, Folder 375)
  - Cortell, Ruth, 1956 (Box 17, Folder 376)
  - Cotter, Walter C., 1959 (Box 17, Folder 377)
  - Countway Library Associates: Hans Zinsser meeting, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 378)
  - Cox, Herald R., 1947, 1952-1962, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 379)
    See also: box 1, folder 11 See also: box 42, folder 1012
  - Cox, Warren M., 1937 (Box 18, Folder 380)
  - Coyne, Catherine, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 381)
  - Craig, John M., 1958-1959, undated (Box 18, Folder 382)
  - Cramer, Robert, 1953-1954, 1957, undated (Box 18, Folder 383)
  - CRC Press, Inc., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 384)
  - Creamer, Warren M., 1965 (Box 18, Folder 385)
  - Creech, Hugh J., 1942-1946 (Box 18, Folder 386)
  - Crile, George, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 387)
  - Crocker, Thomas T., 1948 (Box 18, Folder 388)
  - Crothers, Bronson, 1953, undated (Box 18, Folder 389)
  - Cruikshank, Robert, 1960-1961 (Box 18, Folder 390)
  - Culbertson, Clyde F., 1971 (Box 18, Folder 391)
  - Cunningham, Ira J., 1949 (Box 18, Folder 392)
  - Curelli, Ernest, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 393)
  - Curnen, Edward C., 1945, 1956-1959, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 394)
    See also: box 1, folder 20 See also: box 50, folder 1212
  - Curran, Jean, 1965-1966, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 395)
  - Curtis, Charles P., 1959, undated (Box 18, Folder 396)
  - Cushing, Edward H., 1943-1944, 1954-1962 (Box 18, Folder 397)
  - Cushing Veterans Administration Hospital, 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 398)
  - Cutter Laboratories, 1949-1950, 1955-1962, 1965, undated (Box 18, Folder 399)
  - Dale, Paul W., 1946, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 400)
  - Dalldorf, Gilbert, 1953-1963, 1967, 1975, undated (Box 18, Folder 401)
  - Dameshek, William, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 402)
  - Dammin, Gustave J., 1967-1968, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 403)
  - Damon Runyan Memorial Fund, 1968-1969, undated (Box 18, Folder 404)
  - D'Angio, G. J., 1944 (Box 18, Folder 405)
  - Daniels, Joan, 1947, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 406)
  - Dann, Alexander, 1956 (Box 18, Folder 407)
  - Dausset, Jean, 1970-1971, undated (Box 18, Folder 408)
  - Davidson, Richard, 1971-1974, undated (Box 18, Folder 409)
  - Davies, Warren L., 1947 (Box 18, Folder 410)
  - Davies Fund, 1964-1966, 1969, 1981-1982, undated (Box 18, Folder 411)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1955-1967 (Box 18, Folder 412)
  - Davis, Bernard D., 1969-1976, undated (Box 18, Folder 413)
  - Day, George Parmly, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 414)
  - De Barbieri, A., 1962 (Box 18, Folder 415)
  - Debré, Robert, 1961-1962, 1965-1969 (Box 19, Folder 416)
  - Debré, Robert, 1970-1974, undated (Box 19, Folder 417)
  - de Carvalho, S., 1959, 1965, undated (Box 19, Folder 418)
  - Deinhardt, Freidrich, 1955-1958 (Box 19, Folder 419)
  - Deke Ouarterly, 1956-1958 (Box 19, Folder 420)
  - Dekking, Fritz, 1956-1961, 1965-1968, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 421)
  - Delay, Paul D., 1965 (Box 19, Folder 422)
  - Delbrück, M., 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 423)
  - De Maeyer, Edward, 1958-1964, 1968-1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 424-426)
  - Dengue fever, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 427)
  - Denny-Brown, Derek, 1946-1947, 1954-1955 (Box 19, Folder 428)
  - Deotto, Romolo, 1960, undated (Box 19, Folder 429)
  - Detroit-6: cultivation and maintenance, 1957, undated (Box 19, Folder 430)
  - Deutsche Akademie der Naturforscher Leopoldina, 1952, 1957-1958, 1967, 1975-1977, undated (Box 19, Folder 431)
  - Deutscher Erfinder Verband, 1963-1966, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 432)
  - Diamandopoulos, George Th., 1962-1974, 1977-1979, undated (Box 20, Folder 433-437)
  - Diamond, Louis K., 1946-1947, 1963-1965, 1971, 1977, undated (Box 20, Folder 438)
  - Diarrhea, 1947, 1969, undated (Box 20, Folder 439)
  - Dick, George W. A., 1949, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 440)
  - Dictionary of American Biography, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 441)
  - Diener, Theodor O., 1972-1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 442)
  - Dieselmedaillen-Kuratorium, 1961-1964, undated (Box 20, Folder 443)
  - Dingle, John H., 1946-1953, 1957-1959, 1965, undated (Box 20, Folder 444)
  - Dinner Club, 1955-1959, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 445)
  - Dmochowski, Leon, 1959, 1964-1965, 1971-1974 (Box 20, Folder 446)
  - Dmochowski, Leon, undated (Box 21, Folder 447)
  - Dohan, Francis C., 1968-1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 448)
  - Donald, Heather B., 1956 (Box 21, Folder 449)
  - Donohoe, Patricia, 1974, undated (Box 21, Folder 450)
  - Dorsey, Joseph L., 1965 (Box 21, Folder 451)
  - Doull, James A., 1957-1958 (Box 21, Folder 452)
  - Downie, Allan W., 1953, 1957, 1961-1964, 1967, undated (Box 21, Folder 453)
  - Drinker, Cecil K. and Katherine, 1939-1947, 1951, 1955-1956, 1959, undated (Box 21, Folder 454)
  - Drozdov, Sergei G., 1968 (Box 21, Folder 455)
  - Dubes, George R., 1957 (Box 21, Folder 456)
  - Dublin, T. D., 1943 (Box 21, Folder 457)
  - Dubos, René J., 1941-1953, 1961, 1967, undated (Box 21, Folder 458)
  - Duck plague virus, 1969-1970, undated (Box 21, Folder 459)
  - Dudgeon, J. Alistair, 1958-1960, 1964-1965, 1973, undated (Box 21, Folder 460)
  - Duff, James T., 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 461)
  - Duke University, 1967, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 462)
  - Dulbecco, Renato, 1951-1952, 1957-1958, 1966, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 463)
  - Dull, H. Bruce, 1960-1966, 1969, 1973-1974 (Box 21, Folder 464)
  - Dunlop, Derrick, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 465)
  - Dunlop, W. R., 1958 (Box 21, Folder 466)
  - Duran-Reynals, F., 1955 (Box 21, Folder 467)
  - Duzak, Edward J., 1941, 1946 (Box 21, Folder 468)
  - E. F. Mahady Company, 1947-1948, 1959 (Box 21, Folder 469)
  - Eagle, Harry, 1951-1952, 1958 (Box 21, Folder 470)
  - Eastern equine encephalitis, 1956-1957 (Box 21, Folder 471)
  - Eaton, Monroe D., 1941, 1966-1969 (Box 21, Folder 472)
  - Ebert, Robert H., 1967-1968, 1973, 1976, undated (Box 21, Folder 473)
  - Ecker, E. E., 1940 (Box 21, Folder 474)
  - Edizioni Scientifiche e Tecniche, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 475)
  - Edmunds, Sally, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 476)
  - Edsall, Geoffrey, 1944-1948, 1955, 1958-1972, undated (Box 21, Folder 477)
  - Edsall, John, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 478)
  - Eichenwald, Heinz F., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 479)
  - Eichlseder, Walter, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 480)
  - Einhorn, Sidney, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 481)
  - Eley, R. Cannon, 1956 (Box 22, Folder 482)
  - Elkeles, Gerardo, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 483)
  - Elsevier Publishing Co., 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 484)
  - Encyclopedia Americana, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 485)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 486)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica Films, 1945, undated (Box 22, Folder 487)
  - Enjalbert, Lise, 1949-1950, 1957-1959, 1962-1964, 1970-1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 488)
  - Eppinger, Eugene C., 1946 (Box 22, Folder 489)
  - Epstein, M. Anthony, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 490)
  - Equipment
    - A. Gallenkamp & Co., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 491)
    - A. H. Thomas Company, 1943 (Box 22, Folder 492)
    - Armour Laboratories, 1953, 1959, 1966-1967 (Box 22, Folder 493)
    - Barnstead Still & Sterilizer Co., Inc., 1951, 1957-1961, undated (Box 22, Folder 494)
    - Beckman Instruments, Inc., 1960-1967, undated (Box 22, Folder 495)
    - Bellco Glass, Inc., 1965-1966, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 496)
    - Corning Glass, 1959-1960, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 497)
    - Cudahy Laboratories, 1954-1955, 1959-1961 (Box 22, Folder 498)
    - Custom Scientific Instruments, Inc., 1952 (Box 22, Folder 499)
    - Demuth Glassworks, 1960-1963 (Box 22, Folder 500)
    - Exakta: camera, undated (Box 22, Folder 501)